const STORE = [
	{
		question: "What was Angela Martin's favorite animal?",
		answers: ['Turtles', 'Dogs', 'Cats', 'Birds'],
		correctAnswer: 'Cats'
	},
	{
		question: 'How many kids did Jim and Pam have together?',
		answers: ['2', '3', '4', '5'],
		correctAnswer: '2'
	},
	{
		question: "What was one of Michael Scott's favorite lines?",
		answers: [
			'Cut...it...out!',
			'Did I do that?',
			"That's what she said!",
			"I ain't afraid of no ghosts!"
		],
		correctAnswer: "That's what she said"
	},
	{
		question: 'What kind of company was Dunder Mifflin',
		answers: [
			'A cheese company',
			'A pencil company',
			'A credit card company',
			'A paper company'
		],
		correctAnswer: 'A paper company'
	},
	{
		question: 'Which person did Toby Flenderson have feelings for?',
		answers: ['Kelly', 'Pam', 'Angela', 'Phyllis'],
		correctAnswer: 'Pam'
	},
	{
		question: 'Once a year, Stanley looks forward to this day. What is it?',
		answers: ['Pretzel day', 'Cotton candy day', 'lazy day', 'Friendship day'],
		correctAnswer: 'Pretzel day'
	},
	{
		question:
			'Who was the assistant to the regional manager before finally becoming manager?',
		answers: [
			'Michael Scott',
			'Kelly Kapor',
			'Dwight Schrute',
			'Angela Martin'
		],
		correctAnswer: 'Dwight Schrute'
	},
	{
		question: 'What award ceremony did Michael Scott host?',
		answers: [
			'The Office Awards',
			'The Papers',
			'The Dundies',
			'The Coworker Awards'
		],
		correctAnswer: 'The Dundies'
	},
	{
		question: 'Which person pulled the most pranks on Dwight Schrute?',
		answers: ['Jim Halpert', 'Michael Scott', 'Oscar Martinez', 'Kevin Malone'],
		correctAnswer: 'Jim Halpert'
	},
	{
		question:
			'Which person became the Vice President of North Eastern Sales and then got arrested for fraud?',
		answers: ['Oscar Martinez', 'Andy Bernard', 'Ryan Howard', 'Kevin Malone'],
		correctAnswer: 'Ryan Howard'
	}
];
